Who be sippin’ on this? I do
I’m the, I’m the, I’m the, I’m the
I’m the sugar honey ice tea
and you know it
Ice, ice, ice and you know that
I’m the coldest
I’m the sugar honey
I, I, I’m the sugar honey
I’m sweet just like some ice cream
Milk chocolate icing
My life look like a pipe dream
I know, I know, I know
I know I’m so enticing
I make ’em lime green
Temperature rising
Let’s go, let’s go, let’s go
난 부드럽게 너를 녹여버리지
Stop, make no mistake
Hit that stage baby, ain’t the same
Drop, I’m going in
우린 무대 위의 Queen
Monster melody
I’m the sugar honey ice tea
and you know it
Ain’t no other baddie like me,
yeah you know it
I’m the sugar honey
I, I’m the sugar honey ice
Suga mama, don’t do the drama
Just add the commas like
Yuh yuh yuh
Do what I wanna, lil prima donna
Got the wrist on water like
Yuh yuh yuh
Tell me what you know ’bout this
Wanna get like me? You wish
Comes naturally, I know they mad at me
Cuz they know I’m the
I’m sweet just like some ice cream
Milk chocolate icing
My life look like a pipe dream
I know, I know, I know
I know I’m so enticing
I make ’em lime green
Temperature rising
Let’s go, let’s go, let’s go
난 부드럽게 너를 녹여버리지
Stop, make no mistake
Hit that stage baby, ain’t the same
Drop, I’m going in
우린 무대 위의 Queen
Monster melody
I’m the sugar honey ice tea
and you know it
Ain’t no other baddie like me,
yeah you know it
I’m the sugar honey
I, I’m the sugar honey ice
Tasty, yeah I got you comin’ back
Crazy, I give you a heart attack
Baby, tell me what you think about that
What you think about that
I’m the SHHH
Ohh
Sugar honey ice tea
You know it, know it
Sugar honey
I’m the sugar, I’m the sugar
Sugar honey ice tea
You know it, know it
Sugar honey
I’m the sugar, I’m the sugar
Sugar honey, sugar honey,
honey ice tea (Yay yeah)
honey ice tea
I’m the sugar honey
I, I, I’m the sugar honey ice tea